Jennifer Greenhough

12 3 Main Street, Tampa, FL 12 345 j.greenhough@youremail.com (012) 345-6789

Sales manager with over eight years of experience recruiting, training, and supervising sales staff. Proven track record in securing customer Loyalty and increasing product distribution. Exceptional coach and mentor, able to build top-performing sales teams.

Education

Bachelor of Arts in Business Administration

University of Florida, Miami, FL September 2006 -June 2010

MBA Specializing in Marketing

University of Florida, Miami, FL September 2010-June 2012

Key Skills

- Excellent Communication
- Team Leadership
- Conflict Resolution
- Exceptional Customer Service
- MS Office Suite
- Organized
- Punctual
- Point of Sales Knowledge
- Staff Training
- Excellent Motivator
- Merchandising Knowledge

Professional Experience

Sales Manager

ABC Clothing. Tampa. FL I August 2016 - Present

- Supervise, recruit, and train a team of up to 40 sales staff
- Introduce a new customer loyalty program that increased sales by 22% in 2019 and increased customer satisfaction by 31%.
- Develop quarterly sales campaigns in accordance with marketing budgets
- Assist in the development of an online and app store that increased profits by 14% in the first year.
- ♦ Discuss new product lines with key suppliers

Associate Sales Manager

National Pool Supplies, Orlando, FL | July 2012 - July 2016

- Organized and set up displays to maintain the visual appeal of the main store
- Awarded Employee of the year in 2015
- Supervised the delivery and installation of swimming pools to clients in the Orlando area.
- Trained new sales associates in company procedures, product lines, and selling techniques
- Worked on monthly online and mail advertising campaigns
- Surpasses sales goals by 17% in 2014 and 28% in 2015